<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ImmersiveDetailSample</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="immersivedetailsample">Single Activity</string>
    <string name="immersivedetailfragmentactivity">Activity with fragment</string>
    <string name="pager_bullet_separator" formatted="false">%s / %s</string>

    <string name="long_text">On March 9, 2016, ahead of the Google I/O developer conference, Google released the first alpha version of Android N as part of a new Android Beta Program intended for testing by developers and enthusiasts before official release this summer. The developer preview builds were compatible with only current Google Nexus devices; the 5X, 6P, 6, 9, Pixel C, and Nexus Player. The Android Beta Program that was introduced allows testers to opt-in for over-the-air updates to new beta versions as they are released.On April 13, 2016, Android N Beta Preview 2 was released. Google further discussed Android N during the I/O keynote on May 18, 2016, and unveiled its new virtual reality platform, Daydream. Beta Preview 3, the first preview release deemed suitable for wider public beta testing, was released at this time. Google also announced that it would hold a contest to determine the official release name of the operating system.Beta Preview 4 was released on June 15, 2016. On June 30, 2016, Google announced that N\'s release name would be Nougat; it was also confirmed that Nougat would be version 7.0 of Android.The final Beta Preview, 5, was released on July 18, 2016.Android 7.0 was officially released on August 22, 2016, with the Nexus 6, 5X, 6P, 9, Nexus Player, Pixel C, and General Mobile 4G as the first devices to receive the update. Dave Burke, Android\'s Vice President of Engineering, stated in August 2016 that updates to Nougat would be released quarterly as maintenance releases focusing on continued refinements and polish.On September 6, 2016, LG announced the V20, the first smartphone to ship with Nougat pre-installed. Google unveiled the first-party Pixel and Pixel XL smartphones during a hardware-focused event on October 4, 2016, with the Pixel phones replacing the Nexus series.Updates to existing devices vary by manufacturer and carrier, and driver support for the version by the manufacturer of a device\'s respective system-on-chip. Major manufacturers, including HTC, Sony, and Motorola announced intents to update a range of their recent devices to Nougat. Qualcomm stated that it would not support Nougat on devices using its Snapdragon 800 and 801 system-on-chips for undisclosed reasons. Although developer preview builds of Nougat were released for the device, Sony stated that it would not upgrade the Xperia Z3  which uses the Snapdragon 801 to the final version due to unforeseen platform limitations. It was reported that the Google Compatibility Test Suite  whose tests must be passed in order to receive official certification specified that all devices running Nougat must support either Vulkan or OpenGL ES 3.1 graphics APIs neither of which are supported by the device\'s Adreno 330 graphics core.A post-release update known as Android 7.1 was pre-loaded onto Google\'s Pixel and Pixel XL smartphones released in October 2016;the new version adds support for the Google Daydream VR platform, image keyboards, expanded emoji support including male and female versions of gendered emoji, support for actions to be displayed in menus on home screen app shortcuts, and other new features. A preview of 7.1 for existing Nexus devices was released via Android Beta Program later in the month, and officially released as Android 7.1.1 on December 5, 2016. As of 7.1.1, the Nexus 6 and Nexus 9 are now considered end-of-life, and do not receive any further updates. Android 7.1.2 was released in April 2017, providing various improvements and minor functionality improvements to Nexus and Pixel-branded devices.As of June 2017, 10% of devices that access Google Play run Nougat.Nougat redesigns the notification shade, which now features a smaller row of icons for settings, replacing notification cards with a new sheet design, and allowing inline replies for notifications. This feature is implemented via existing APIs that are used for similar functionality on Android Wear. Multiple notifications from a single app can also be bundled, and there is greater per-app control over notifications.A split-screen display mode was introduced for phones, in which two apps can be snapped to occupy halves of the screen. An experimental multi-window mode is also available as a hidden feature, where multiple apps can appear simultaneously on the screen in overlapping windows.The Doze power saving mechanism introduced in Android Marshmallow was expanded to include a state activated when the device is running on battery and the screen has been off for a period of time but is not stationary. In this state, network activity is restricted, and apps are granted maintenance windows in which they can access the network and perform background tasks. As in Marshmallow, the full Doze state is activated if the device is stationary with its screen off for a period of time. A new Data Saver mode restricts background mobile data usage, and can trigger internal functions in apps that are designed to reduce bandwidth usage, such as capping the quality of streaming media. In December 2015, Google announced that Android Nougat would switch its Java Runtime Environment from the defunct Apache Harmony to OpenJDK the official open source implementation of the Java platform maintained by Oracle Corporation and the Java community. The Android Runtime  ART now incorporates a profile-guided compilation system, utilizing a JIT compiler and profiling alongside its current ahead-of-time compiler to further optimize apps for a device\'s hardware and other conditions in the background.Nougat introduces a system for enabling seamless, automatic system updates, based upon and sharing some code with the implementation of similar functionality on Chrome OS. The system uses a pair of SquashFS partitions; the Android system executes from an online partition, while updates are applied in the background to a redundant offline partition. On the next boot following the installation of an update, the redundant partition is designated as active, and the device henceforth boots into the updated system. The previous system partition is kept as a backup in case of update failure, and to serve as the offline partition for the next update. This system removes the requirement for the device to reboot into the system recovery environment to apply the update  which prevents the device from being used until the update is complete and also provides the ability for an update to be automatically rolled back in case of a failure. Due to the partitioning requirements of this system, existing devices will not support seamless updates. Additionally, due to the ART changes on Nougat, apps no longer need to be re-compiled upon the first boot after a system update.Developer Preview 2 added platform support for Vulkan, the new low-level 3D-rendering API to augment OpenGL ES but with higher graphics performance.Nougat is the first version featuring Unicode 9.0 support and comes with updated emoji plus support for emoji skin tones.Android 7.1 adds native API support for implementing image keyboards; multi-endpoint telephony; shortcut menus and rounded icon assets for apps on launchers; and support for the Google Daydream virtual reality platform.The Google Daydream feature is a specific VR mode, with advanced technology for reduced graphics latency, a sustained performance mode to assist developers in optimizing apps to a device\'s thermal profile, a new head tracking algorithm which combines the input from various device sensors, and integration of system notifications into the VR user interface.</string>
</resources>
